<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Engineering Digest</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yourusername/eng-digest</link>
    <description>Daily digest of engineering blog posts from top tech companies</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yourusername/eng-digest/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 09:27:02 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Eng Digest</generator>
    <item>
      <title>Building AI Agents with Google Gemini 3 and Open Source Frameworks</title>
      <link>https://developers.googleblog.com/building-ai-agents-with-google-gemini-3-and-open-source-frameworks/</link>
      <description>New agentic features include `thinking_level` for reasoning control, Stateful Tool Use via Thought Signatures, and `media_resolution` for multimodal fidelity It has Day 0 support for open-source frameworks like LangChain, AI SDK, LlamaIndex, Pydantic AI, and n8n Best practices include simplifying prompts and keeping temperature at 1.0.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 09:26:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://developers.googleblog.com/building-ai-agents-with-google-gemini-3-and-open-source-frameworks/</guid>
      <source>Google Developers</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building with Gemini 3 in Jules</title>
      <link>https://developers.googleblog.com/jules-gemini-3/</link>
      <description>Jules, an always-on, multi-step software development agent, now features Gemini 3, offering clearer reasoning and better reliability Upcoming features include directory attachment without GitHub and automatic PR creation Jules aims to reduce software writing overhead so developers can focus on building.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 09:26:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://developers.googleblog.com/jules-gemini-3/</guid>
      <source>Google Developers</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building production AI on Google Cloud TPUs with JAX</title>
      <link>https://developers.googleblog.com/building-production-ai-on-google-cloud-tpus-with-jax/</link>
      <description>The JAX AI Stack is a modular, industrial-grade, end-to-end machine learning platform built on the core JAX library, co-designed with Cloud TPUs It features key components like JAX, Flax, Optax, and Orbax for foundational model development, plus an extended ecosystem for the full ML lifecycle and production This integration provides a powerful, scalable foundation for AI development, delivering significant performance advantages.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 09:26:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://developers.googleblog.com/building-production-ai-on-google-cloud-tpus-with-jax/</guid>
      <source>Google Developers</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What AI is actually good for, according to developers</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/ai-and-ml/generative-ai/what-ai-is-actually-good-for-according-to-developers/</link>
      <description>AI is designed to help you do what you love most, not replace your expertise Discover how developer feedback and real-world experience are shaping AI coding tools that keep you in control The post What AI is actually good for, according to developers appeared first on The GitHub Blog.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:39:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.blog/ai-and-ml/generative-ai/what-ai-is-actually-good-for-according-to-developers/</guid>
      <source>GitHub Blog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSS at Scale With StyleX</title>
      <link>https://engineering.fb.com/2026/01/12/web/css-at-scale-with-stylex/</link>
      <description>It’s no different at Meta, which is why we open-sourced StyleX, a solution for CSS at scale StyleX combines the ergonomics of CSS-in-JS with the performance of static CSS The post CSS at Scale With StyleX appeared first on Engineering at Meta.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:34:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://engineering.fb.com/2026/01/12/web/css-at-scale-with-stylex/</guid>
      <source>Meta Engineering</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: AWS Lambda for .NET 10, AWS Client VPN quickstart, Best of AWS re:Invent, and more (January 12, 2026)</title>
      <link>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-aws-lambda-for-net-10-aws-client-vpn-quickstart-best-of-aws-reinvent-and-more-january-12-2026/</link>
      <description>At the beginning of January, I tend to set my top resolutions for the year, a way to focus on what I want to achieve If AI and cloud computing are on your resolution list, consider creating an AWS Free Tier account to receive up to $200 in credits and have 6 months of risk-free […]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:39:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-aws-lambda-for-net-10-aws-client-vpn-quickstart-best-of-aws-reinvent-and-more-january-12-2026/</guid>
      <source>AWS News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Want better AI outputs? Try context engineering.</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/ai-and-ml/generative-ai/want-better-ai-outputs-try-context-engineering/</link>
      <description>Learn how custom instructions, reusable prompts, and custom agents help GitHub Copilot deliver more accurate results The post Want better AI outputs Try context engineering. appeared first on The GitHub Blog.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.blog/ai-and-ml/generative-ai/want-better-ai-outputs-try-context-engineering/</guid>
      <source>GitHub Blog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Light waves, rising tides, and drifting ships: Game Off 2025 winners</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/open-source/gaming/light-waves-rising-tides-and-drifting-ships-game-off-2025-winners/</link>
      <description>Out of more than 700 games submitted to Game Off 2025, these ten winners stand out for creativity, craft, and bold interpretations of the WAVES theme All are free to play, with source code available to explore The post Light waves, rising tides, and drifting ships: Game Off 2025 winners appeared first on The GitHub Blog.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 21:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.blog/open-source/gaming/light-waves-rising-tides-and-drifting-ships-game-off-2025-winners/</guid>
      <source>GitHub Blog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy New Year! AWS Weekly Roundup: 10,000 AIdeas Competition, Amazon EC2, Amazon ECS Managed Instances and more (January 5, 2026)</title>
      <link>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/happy-new-year-aws-weekly-roundup-10000-aideas-competition-amazon-ec2-amazon-ecs-managed-instances-and-more-january-5-2026/</link>
      <description>I hope the holidays gave you time to recharge and spend time with your loved ones Like every year, I took a few weeks off after AWS re:Invent to rest and plan ahead I used some of that downtime to plan the next cohort for Become a Solutions Architect (BeSA)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:10:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/happy-new-year-aws-weekly-roundup-10000-aideas-competition-amazon-ec2-amazon-ecs-managed-instances-and-more-january-5-2026/</guid>
      <source>AWS News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python Typing Survey 2025: Code Quality and Flexibility As Top Reasons for Typing Adoption</title>
      <link>https://engineering.fb.com/2025/12/22/developer-tools/python-typing-survey-2025-code-quality-flexibility-typing-adoption/</link>
      <description>The 2025 Typed Python Survey, conducted by contributors from JetBrains, Meta, and the broader Python typing community, offers a comprehensive look at the current state of Python’s type system and developer tooling With 1,241 responses (a 15% increase from last year), the survey captures the evolving sentiment, challenges, and opportunities around Python typing in the [...] Read More The post Python Typing Survey 2025: Code Quality and Flexibility As Top Reasons for Typing Adoption appeared first on Engineering at Meta.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 14:00:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://engineering.fb.com/2025/12/22/developer-tools/python-typing-survey-2025-code-quality-flexibility-typing-adoption/</guid>
      <source>Meta Engineering</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DrP: Meta’s Root Cause Analysis Platform at Scale</title>
      <link>https://engineering.fb.com/2025/12/19/data-infrastructure/drp-metas-root-cause-analysis-platform-at-scale/</link>
      <description>Incident investigation can be a daunting task in today’s digital landscape, where large-scale systems comprise numerous interconnected components and dependencies DrP is a root cause analysis (RCA) platform, designed by Meta, to programmatically automate the investigation process, significantly reducing the mean time to resolve (MTTR) for incidents and alleviating on-call toil Today, DrP is used [...] Read More The post DrP: Meta’s Root Cause Analysis Platform at Scale appeared first on Engineering at Meta.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:35:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://engineering.fb.com/2025/12/19/data-infrastructure/drp-metas-root-cause-analysis-platform-at-scale/</guid>
      <source>Meta Engineering</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the feature store powering real-time AI in Dropbox Dash</title>
      <link>https://dropbox.tech/machine-learning/feature-store-powering-realtime-ai-in-dropbox-dash</link>
      <description>The feature store is a critical part of how we rank and retrieve the right context across your work.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dropbox.tech/machine-learning/feature-store-powering-realtime-ai-in-dropbox-dash</guid>
      <source>Dropbox Engineering</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stripe Atlas startups in 2025: Year in review</title>
      <link>https://stripe.com/blog/stripe-atlas-startups-in-2025-year-in-review</link>
      <description>2025 was a breakout year for early-stage startups, as founders launched more companies and generated revenue faster than ever Three shifts stand out: customer bases are more international than ever, time-to-revenue has compressed, and founders are turning their attention to AI agents over AI infrastructure or copilots.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://stripe.com/blog/stripe-atlas-startups-in-2025-year-in-review</guid>
      <source>Stripe Engineering</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Businesses grow revenue on Stripe 27 percentage points faster after accepting financing through Stripe Capital</title>
      <link>https://stripe.com/blog/businesses-grow-revenue-on-stripe-faster-after-accepting-financing-through-stripe-capital</link>
      <description>In a new study, we found a strong causal relationship between accepting financing and growing revenue on Stripe Learn which businesses are most likely to benefit, and how greater access to financing could drive significant GDP growth.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://stripe.com/blog/businesses-grow-revenue-on-stripe-faster-after-accepting-financing-through-stripe-capital</guid>
      <source>Stripe Engineering</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing next-day settlement, a faster way to access your earnings</title>
      <link>https://docs.stripe.com/payouts/next-day-settlement</link>
      <description>Gain next-day access to cash, and use funds where they’re needed most Get reliable auto-settlement in a few clicks right from the Dashboard.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://docs.stripe.com/payouts/next-day-settlement</guid>
      <source>Stripe Engineering</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Temporal Powers Reliable Cloud Operations at Netflix</title>
      <link>https://netflixtechblog.com/how-temporal-powers-reliable-cloud-operations-at-netflix-73c69ccb5953?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4</link>
      <description>Clouddriver’s job is to decompose and execute Cloud Operations sent to it by Orca as part of a deployment Ultimately, we decided to pull the trigger on migrating Cloud Operation execution to Temporal.Cloud Operations with TemporalToday, we execute Cloud Operations as Temporal workflows We built a CloudOperationRunner interface in Orca to encapsulate whether the Cloud Operation was being executed via the legacy path or Temporal</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 23:51:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netflixtechblog.com/how-temporal-powers-reliable-cloud-operations-at-netflix-73c69ccb5953?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4</guid>
      <source>Netflix TechBlog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix Live Origin</title>
      <link>https://netflixtechblog.com/netflix-live-origin-41f1b0ad5371?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4</link>
      <description>This defect information is provided as metadata when the segment is published to the live origin This combination of cache and highly available storage has met the demanding needs of our Live Origin for over a year now.Storage System High Level ArchitectureDelivering this consistent low latency for large writes with cross-region replication and consistent write-through caching to a distributed cache required solving numerous hard problems with novel techniques, which we plan to share in detail during a future post.Scalability and scalable architectureNetflix’s live streaming platform must handle a high volume of diverse stream renditions for each live event This metadata caching complements the storage system’s distributed media cache, providing a complete solution for traffic surge protection.SummaryThe Netflix Live Origin, built upon an optimized storage platform, is specifically designed for live streaming</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 17:38:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netflixtechblog.com/netflix-live-origin-41f1b0ad5371?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4</guid>
      <source>Netflix TechBlog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon ECS, Amazon CloudWatch, Amazon Cognito and more (December 15, 2025)</title>
      <link>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-amazon-ecs-amazon-cloudwatch-amazon-cognito-and-more-december-15-2025/</link>
      <description>We’re nearly at the end of 2025 And what a year it’s been From re:Invent recap events, to AWS Summits, AWS Innovate, AWS re:Inforce, Community Days, and DevDays and, recently, adding that cherry on the cake, re:Invent 2025, we have lived through a year filled with exciting moments and technology advancements […]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 16:42:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-amazon-ecs-amazon-cloudwatch-amazon-cognito-and-more-december-15-2025/</guid>
      <source>AWS News</source>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
