<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Engineering Digest</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yourusername/eng-digest</link>
    <description>Daily digest of engineering blog posts from top tech companies</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yourusername/eng-digest/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:28:24 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Eng Digest</generator>
    <item>
      <title>Building with Gemini 3 in Jules</title>
      <link>https://developers.googleblog.com/jules-gemini-3/</link>
      <description>Jules, an always-on, multi-step software development agent, now features Gemini 3, offering clearer reasoning and better reliability Upcoming features include directory attachment without GitHub and automatic PR creation Jules aims to reduce software writing overhead so developers can focus on building.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://developers.googleblog.com/jules-gemini-3/</guid>
      <source>Google Developers</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building production AI on Google Cloud TPUs with JAX</title>
      <link>https://developers.googleblog.com/building-production-ai-on-google-cloud-tpus-with-jax/</link>
      <description>The JAX AI Stack is a modular, industrial-grade, end-to-end machine learning platform built on the core JAX library, co-designed with Cloud TPUs It features key components like JAX, Flax, Optax, and Orbax for foundational model development, plus an extended ecosystem for the full ML lifecycle and production This integration provides a powerful, scalable foundation for AI development, delivering significant performance advantages.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://developers.googleblog.com/building-production-ai-on-google-cloud-tpus-with-jax/</guid>
      <source>Google Developers</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build with Google Antigravity, our new agentic development platform</title>
      <link>https://developers.googleblog.com/build-with-google-antigravity-our-new-agentic-development-platform/</link>
      <description>Introducing Google Antigravity, a new agentic development platform for orchestrating code It combines an AI-powered Editor View with a Manager Surface to deploy agents that autonomously plan, execute, and verify complex tasks across your editor, terminal, and browser Agents communicate progress via Artifacts (screenshots, recordings) for easy verification</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://developers.googleblog.com/build-with-google-antigravity-our-new-agentic-development-platform/</guid>
      <source>Google Developers</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build an agent into any app with the GitHub Copilot SDK</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/news-insights/company-news/build-an-agent-into-any-app-with-the-github-copilot-sdk/</link>
      <description>Now in technical preview, the GitHub Copilot SDK can plan, invoke tools, edit files, and run commands as a programmable layer you can use in any application The post Build an agent into any app with the GitHub Copilot SDK appeared first on The GitHub Blog.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.blog/news-insights/company-news/build-an-agent-into-any-app-with-the-github-copilot-sdk/</guid>
      <source>GitHub Blog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A cheat sheet to slash commands in GitHub Copilot CLI</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/ai-and-ml/github-copilot/a-cheat-sheet-to-slash-commands-in-github-copilot-cli/</link>
      <description>Run tests, fix code, and get support—right in your workflow Stay focused and let Copilot handle the busywork The post A cheat sheet to slash commands in GitHub Copilot CLI appeared first on The GitHub Blog.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:09:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.blog/ai-and-ml/github-copilot/a-cheat-sheet-to-slash-commands-in-github-copilot-cli/</guid>
      <source>GitHub Blog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Amazon EC2 G7e instances accelerated by NVIDIA RTX PRO 6000 Blackwell Server Edition GPUs</title>
      <link>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-amazon-ec2-g7e-instances-accelerated-by-nvidia-rtx-pro-6000-blackwell-server-edition-gpus/</link>
      <description>AWS introduces Amazon EC2 G7e instances accelerated by the NVIDIA RTX PRO 6000 Blackwell Server Edition GPUs with up to 2.3 times inference performance G7e instances deliver cost-effective performance for generative AI inference workloads and the highest performance for graphics workloads.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:22:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-amazon-ec2-g7e-instances-accelerated-by-nvidia-rtx-pro-6000-blackwell-server-edition-gpus/</guid>
      <source>AWS News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-supported vulnerability triage with the GitHub Security Lab Taskflow Agent</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/security/ai-supported-vulnerability-triage-with-the-github-security-lab-taskflow-agent/</link>
      <description>Learn how we are using the newly released GitHub Security Lab Taskflow Agent to triage categories of vulnerabilities in GitHub Actions and JavaScript projects The post AI-supported vulnerability triage with the GitHub Security Lab Taskflow Agent appeared first on The GitHub Blog.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:52:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.blog/security/ai-supported-vulnerability-triage-with-the-github-security-lab-taskflow-agent/</guid>
      <source>GitHub Blog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Kiro CLI latest features, AWS European Sovereign Cloud, EC2 X8i instances, and more (January 19, 2026)</title>
      <link>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-kiro-cli-latest-features-aws-european-sovereign-cloud-ec2-x8i-instances-and-more-january-19-2026/</link>
      <description>At the end of 2025 I was happy to take a long break to enjoy the incredible summers that the southern hemisphere provides I’m back and writing my first post in 2026 which also happens to be my last post for the AWS News Blog (more on this later) The AWS community is starting the […]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 00:24:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-kiro-cli-latest-features-aws-european-sovereign-cloud-ec2-x8i-instances-and-more-january-19-2026/</guid>
      <source>AWS News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The three biggest agentic commerce trends from NRF 2026</title>
      <link>https://stripe.com/blog/three-agentic-commerce-trends-nrf-2026</link>
      <description>Not only are the majority of retailers actively implementing, or have plans to implement, agentic commerce, but many are also moving to a more tactical phase of optimizing their setup—refining their product catalog strategy to launch faster and investing in their own agentic shopping experiences in addition to integrating with third-party agents.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://stripe.com/blog/three-agentic-commerce-trends-nrf-2026</guid>
      <source>Stripe Engineering</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon EC2 X8i instances powered by custom Intel Xeon 6 processors are generally available for memory-intensive workloads</title>
      <link>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-ec2-x8i-instances-powered-by-custom-intel-xeon-6-processors-are-generally-available-for-memory-intensive-workloads/</link>
      <description>AWS is announcing the general availability of Amazon EC2 X8i instances, next-generation memory optimized instances powered by custom Intel Xeon 6 processors available only on AWS X8i instances are SAP-certified and deliver the highest performance and fastest memory bandwidth among comparable Intel processors in the cloud.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:52:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-ec2-x8i-instances-powered-by-custom-intel-xeon-6-processors-are-generally-available-for-memory-intensive-workloads/</guid>
      <source>AWS News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapting the Facebook Reels RecSys AI Model Based on User Feedback</title>
      <link>https://engineering.fb.com/2026/01/14/ml-applications/adapting-the-facebook-reels-recsys-ai-model-based-on-user-feedback/</link>
      <description>We’ve improved personalized video recommendations on Facebook Reels by moving beyond metrics such as likes and watch time and directly leveraging user feedback We’re doubling down on personalization, tackling challenges like sparse user data [...] Read More The post Adapting the Facebook Reels RecSys AI Model Based on User Feedback appeared first on Engineering at Meta.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:51:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://engineering.fb.com/2026/01/14/ml-applications/adapting-the-facebook-reels-recsys-ai-model-based-on-user-feedback/</guid>
      <source>Meta Engineering</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSS at Scale With StyleX</title>
      <link>https://engineering.fb.com/2026/01/12/web/css-at-scale-with-stylex/</link>
      <description>It’s no different at Meta, which is why we open-sourced StyleX, a solution for CSS at scale StyleX combines the ergonomics of CSS-in-JS with the performance of static CSS The post CSS at Scale With StyleX appeared first on Engineering at Meta.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:34:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://engineering.fb.com/2026/01/12/web/css-at-scale-with-stylex/</guid>
      <source>Meta Engineering</source>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
