<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Engineering Digest</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yourusername/eng-digest</link>
    <description>Daily digest of engineering blog posts from top tech companies</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yourusername/eng-digest/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 09:19:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Eng Digest</generator>
    <item>
      <title>Building with Gemini 3 in Jules</title>
      <link>https://developers.googleblog.com/jules-gemini-3/</link>
      <description>Jules, an always-on, multi-step software development agent, now features Gemini 3, offering clearer reasoning and better reliability Upcoming features include directory attachment without GitHub and automatic PR creation Jules aims to reduce software writing overhead so developers can focus on building.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 09:18:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://developers.googleblog.com/jules-gemini-3/</guid>
      <source>Google Developers</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building production AI on Google Cloud TPUs with JAX</title>
      <link>https://developers.googleblog.com/building-production-ai-on-google-cloud-tpus-with-jax/</link>
      <description>The JAX AI Stack is a modular, industrial-grade, end-to-end machine learning platform built on the core JAX library, co-designed with Cloud TPUs It features key components like JAX, Flax, Optax, and Orbax for foundational model development, plus an extended ecosystem for the full ML lifecycle and production This integration provides a powerful, scalable foundation for AI development, delivering significant performance advantages.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 09:18:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://developers.googleblog.com/building-production-ai-on-google-cloud-tpus-with-jax/</guid>
      <source>Google Developers</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build with Google Antigravity, our new agentic development platform</title>
      <link>https://developers.googleblog.com/build-with-google-antigravity-our-new-agentic-development-platform/</link>
      <description>Introducing Google Antigravity, a new agentic development platform for orchestrating code It combines an AI-powered Editor View with a Manager Surface to deploy agents that autonomously plan, execute, and verify complex tasks across your editor, terminal, and browser Agents communicate progress via Artifacts (screenshots, recordings) for easy verification</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 09:18:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://developers.googleblog.com/build-with-google-antigravity-our-new-agentic-development-platform/</guid>
      <source>Google Developers</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The three biggest agentic commerce trends from NRF 2026</title>
      <link>https://stripe.com/blog/three-agentic-commerce-trends-nrf-2026</link>
      <description>Not only are the majority of retailers actively implementing, or have plans to implement, agentic commerce, but many are also moving to a more tactical phase of optimizing their setup—refining their product catalog strategy to launch faster and investing in their own agentic shopping experiences in addition to integrating with third-party agents.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://stripe.com/blog/three-agentic-commerce-trends-nrf-2026</guid>
      <source>Stripe Engineering</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon EC2 X8i instances powered by custom Intel Xeon 6 processors are generally available for memory-intensive workloads</title>
      <link>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-ec2-x8i-instances-powered-by-custom-intel-xeon-6-processors-are-generally-available-for-memory-intensive-workloads/</link>
      <description>AWS is announcing the general availability of Amazon EC2 X8i instances, next-generation memory optimized instances powered by custom Intel Xeon 6 processors available only on AWS X8i instances are SAP-certified and deliver the highest performance and fastest memory bandwidth among comparable Intel processors in the cloud.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:52:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-ec2-x8i-instances-powered-by-custom-intel-xeon-6-processors-are-generally-available-for-memory-intensive-workloads/</guid>
      <source>AWS News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building an agentic memory system for GitHub Copilot</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/ai-and-ml/github-copilot/building-an-agentic-memory-system-for-github-copilot/</link>
      <description>Copilot’s cross-agent memory system lets agents learn and improve across your development workflow, starting with coding agent, CLI, and code review The post Building an agentic memory system for GitHub Copilot appeared first on The GitHub Blog.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:31:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.blog/ai-and-ml/github-copilot/building-an-agentic-memory-system-for-github-copilot/</guid>
      <source>GitHub Blog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When protections outlive their purpose: A lesson on managing defense systems at scale</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/engineering/infrastructure/when-protections-outlive-their-purpose-a-lesson-on-managing-defense-systems-at-scale/</link>
      <description>User feedback led us to clean up outdated mitigations See why observability and lifecycle management are critical for defense systems The post When protections outlive their purpose: A lesson on managing defense systems at scale appeared first on The GitHub Blog.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:54:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.blog/engineering/infrastructure/when-protections-outlive-their-purpose-a-lesson-on-managing-defense-systems-at-scale/</guid>
      <source>GitHub Blog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opening the AWS European Sovereign Cloud</title>
      <link>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/opening-the-aws-european-sovereign-cloud/</link>
      <description>Deutsch | English | Español | Français | Italiano As a European citizen, I understand first-hand the importance of digital sovereignty, especially for our public sector organisations and highly regulated industries Today, I’m delighted to share that the AWS European Sovereign Cloud is now generally available to all customers We first announced our plans to […]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:12:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/opening-the-aws-european-sovereign-cloud/</guid>
      <source>AWS News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Availability Report: December 2025</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/news-insights/company-news/github-availability-report-december-2025/</link>
      <description>In December, we experienced five incidents that resulted in degraded performance across GitHub services The post GitHub Availability Report: December 2025 appeared first on The GitHub Blog.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:06:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.blog/news-insights/company-news/github-availability-report-december-2025/</guid>
      <source>GitHub Blog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapting the Facebook Reels RecSys AI Model Based on User Feedback</title>
      <link>https://engineering.fb.com/2026/01/14/ml-applications/adapting-the-facebook-reels-recsys-ai-model-based-on-user-feedback/</link>
      <description>We’ve improved personalized video recommendations on Facebook Reels by moving beyond metrics such as likes and watch time and directly leveraging user feedback We’re doubling down on personalization, tackling challenges like sparse user data [...] Read More The post Adapting the Facebook Reels RecSys AI Model Based on User Feedback appeared first on Engineering at Meta.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:51:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://engineering.fb.com/2026/01/14/ml-applications/adapting-the-facebook-reels-recsys-ai-model-based-on-user-feedback/</guid>
      <source>Meta Engineering</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSS at Scale With StyleX</title>
      <link>https://engineering.fb.com/2026/01/12/web/css-at-scale-with-stylex/</link>
      <description>It’s no different at Meta, which is why we open-sourced StyleX, a solution for CSS at scale StyleX combines the ergonomics of CSS-in-JS with the performance of static CSS The post CSS at Scale With StyleX appeared first on Engineering at Meta.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:34:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://engineering.fb.com/2026/01/12/web/css-at-scale-with-stylex/</guid>
      <source>Meta Engineering</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: AWS Lambda for .NET 10, AWS Client VPN quickstart, Best of AWS re:Invent, and more (January 12, 2026)</title>
      <link>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-aws-lambda-for-net-10-aws-client-vpn-quickstart-best-of-aws-reinvent-and-more-january-12-2026/</link>
      <description>At the beginning of January, I tend to set my top resolutions for the year, a way to focus on what I want to achieve If AI and cloud computing are on your resolution list, consider creating an AWS Free Tier account to receive up to $200 in credits and have 6 months of risk-free […]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:39:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-aws-lambda-for-net-10-aws-client-vpn-quickstart-best-of-aws-reinvent-and-more-january-12-2026/</guid>
      <source>AWS News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python Typing Survey 2025: Code Quality and Flexibility As Top Reasons for Typing Adoption</title>
      <link>https://engineering.fb.com/2025/12/22/developer-tools/python-typing-survey-2025-code-quality-flexibility-typing-adoption/</link>
      <description>The 2025 Typed Python Survey, conducted by contributors from JetBrains, Meta, and the broader Python typing community, offers a comprehensive look at the current state of Python’s type system and developer tooling With 1,241 responses (a 15% increase from last year), the survey captures the evolving sentiment, challenges, and opportunities around Python typing in the [...] Read More The post Python Typing Survey 2025: Code Quality and Flexibility As Top Reasons for Typing Adoption appeared first on Engineering at Meta.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 14:00:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://engineering.fb.com/2025/12/22/developer-tools/python-typing-survey-2025-code-quality-flexibility-typing-adoption/</guid>
      <source>Meta Engineering</source>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
