<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Engineering Digest</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yourusername/eng-digest</link>
    <description>Daily digest of engineering blog posts from top tech companies</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yourusername/eng-digest/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:28:31 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Eng Digest</generator>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the Data Commons Gemini CLI extension</title>
      <link>https://developers.googleblog.com/announcing-the-data-commons-gemini-cli-extension/</link>
      <description>The new Data Commons extension for the Gemini CLI makes accessing public data easier It allows users to ask complex, natural-language questions to query Data Commons&amp;apos; public datasets, grounding LLM responses in authoritative sources to reduce AI hallucinations Data Commons is an organized library of public data from sources like the UN and World Bank</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:28:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://developers.googleblog.com/announcing-the-data-commons-gemini-cli-extension/</guid>
      <source>Google Developers</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Architecting efficient context-aware multi-agent framework for production</title>
      <link>https://developers.googleblog.com/architecting-efficient-context-aware-multi-agent-framework-for-production/</link>
      <description>ADK introduces **Context Engineering** to scale AI agents beyond large context windows It treats context as a compiled view over a tiered, stateful system (**Session, Memory, Artifacts**) This architecture uses explicit processors for transformation, enables efficient compaction and caching, and allows for strict, scoped context handoffs in multi-agent workflows to ensure reliability and cost-effectiveness in production.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:28:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://developers.googleblog.com/architecting-efficient-context-aware-multi-agent-framework-for-production/</guid>
      <source>Google Developers</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MediaTek NPU and LiteRT: Powering the next generation of on-device AI</title>
      <link>https://developers.googleblog.com/mediatek-npu-and-litert-powering-the-next-generation-of-on-device-ai/</link>
      <description>LiteRT and MediaTek are announcing the new LiteRT NeuroPilot Accelerator This is a ground-up successor for the TFLite NeuroPilot delegate, bringing seamless deployment experience, state-of-the-art LLM support, and advanced performance to millions of devices worldwide.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:28:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://developers.googleblog.com/mediatek-npu-and-litert-powering-the-next-generation-of-on-device-ai/</guid>
      <source>Google Developers</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continuous AI in practice: What developers can automate today with agentic CI</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/ai-and-ml/generative-ai/continuous-ai-in-practice-what-developers-can-automate-today-with-agentic-ci/</link>
      <description>Think of Continuous AI as background agents that operate in your repository for tasks that require reasoning The post Continuous AI in practice: What developers can automate today with agentic CI appeared first on The GitHub Blog.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.blog/ai-and-ml/generative-ai/continuous-ai-in-practice-what-developers-can-automate-today-with-agentic-ci/</guid>
      <source>GitHub Blog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon EC2 C8id, M8id, and R8id instances with up to 22.8 TB local NVMe storage are generally available</title>
      <link>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-ec2-c8id-m8id-and-r8id-instances-with-up-to-22-8-tb-local-nvme-storage-are-generally-available/</link>
      <description>AWS launches Amazon EC2 C8id, M8id, and R8id instances backed by NVMe-based SSD block-level instance storage physically connected to the host server These instances offer 3 times more vCPUs, memory, and local storage with up to 22.8TB of local NVMe-backed SSD block-level storage.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 22:31:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-ec2-c8id-m8id-and-r8id-instances-with-up-to-22-8-tb-local-nvme-storage-are-generally-available/</guid>
      <source>AWS News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Display? No Problem: Cross-Device Passkey Authentication for XR Devices</title>
      <link>https://engineering.fb.com/2026/02/04/security/cross-device-passkey-authentication-for-xr-devices-meta-quest/</link>
      <description>We’re sharing a novel approach to enabling cross-device passkey authentication for devices with inaccessible displays (like XR devices) Our approach bypasses the use of QR codes and enables cross-device authentication without the need for an on-device display, while still complying with all trust and proximity requirements No Problem: Cross-Device Passkey Authentication for XR Devices appeared first on Engineering at Meta.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 22:00:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://engineering.fb.com/2026/02/04/security/cross-device-passkey-authentication-for-xr-devices-meta-quest/</guid>
      <source>Meta Engineering</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pick your agent: Use Claude and Codex on Agent HQ</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/news-insights/company-news/pick-your-agent-use-claude-and-codex-on-agent-hq/</link>
      <description>Claude by Anthropic and OpenAI Codex are now available in public preview on GitHub and VS Code with a Copilot Pro+ or Copilot Enterprise subscription Here&amp;apos;s what you need to know and how to get started today The post Pick your agent: Use Claude and Codex on Agent HQ appeared first on The GitHub Blog.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:00:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.blog/news-insights/company-news/pick-your-agent-use-claude-and-codex-on-agent-hq/</guid>
      <source>GitHub Blog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS IAM Identity Center now supports multi-Region replication for AWS account access and application use</title>
      <link>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-iam-identity-center-now-supports-multi-region-replication-for-aws-account-access-and-application-use/</link>
      <description>AWS IAM Identity Center now supports multi-Region replication of workforce identities and permission sets, enabling improved resiliency for AWS account access and allowing applications to be deployed closer to users while meeting data residency requirements.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 19:13:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-iam-identity-center-now-supports-multi-region-replication-for-aws-account-access-and-application-use/</guid>
      <source>AWS News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What the fastest-growing tools reveal about how software is being built</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/news-insights/octoverse/what-the-fastest-growing-tools-reveal-about-how-software-is-being-built/</link>
      <description>What languages are growing fastest, and why What about the projects that people are interested in the most The post What the fastest-growing tools reveal about how software is being built appeared first on The GitHub Blog.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.blog/news-insights/octoverse/what-the-fastest-growing-tools-reveal-about-how-software-is-being-built/</guid>
      <source>GitHub Blog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon Bedrock agent workflows, Amazon SageMaker private connectivity, and more (February 2, 2026)</title>
      <link>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-amazon-bedrock-agent-workflows-amazon-sagemaker-private-connectivity-and-more-february-2-2026/</link>
      <description>Over the past week, we passed Laba festival, a traditional marker in the Chinese calendar that signals the final stretch leading up to the Lunar New Year For many in China, it’s a moment associated with reflection and preparation, wrapping up what the year has carried, and turning attention toward what lies ahead</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:19:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-amazon-bedrock-agent-workflows-amazon-sagemaker-private-connectivity-and-more-february-2-2026/</guid>
      <source>AWS News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engineering VP Josh Clemm on how we use knowledge graphs, MCP, and DSPy in Dash</title>
      <link>https://dropbox.tech/machine-learning/vp-josh-clemm-knowledge-graphs-mcp-and-dspy-dash</link>
      <description>Engineering VP Josh Clemm deep-dives into how we think about knowledge graphs, indexes, MCP, and prompt optimization using tools like DSPy.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dropbox.tech/machine-learning/vp-josh-clemm-knowledge-graphs-mcp-and-dspy-dash</guid>
      <source>Dropbox Engineering</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rust at Scale: An Added Layer of Security for WhatsApp</title>
      <link>https://engineering.fb.com/2026/01/27/security/rust-at-scale-security-whatsapp/</link>
      <description>WhatsApp has adopted and rolled out a new layer of security for users – built with Rust – as part of its effort to harden defenses against malware threats WhatsApp’s experience creating and distributing our media consistency library in Rust to billions of devices and browsers proves Rust is production ready at a global scale. [...] Read More The post Rust at Scale: An Added Layer of Security for WhatsApp appeared first on Engineering at Meta.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:00:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://engineering.fb.com/2026/01/27/security/rust-at-scale-security-whatsapp/</guid>
      <source>Meta Engineering</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AI Evolution of Graph Search at Netflix</title>
      <link>https://netflixtechblog.com/the-ai-evolution-of-graph-search-at-netflix-d416ec5b1151?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4</link>
      <description>We need the LLM to generate a Graph Search Filter DSL statement that is syntactically, semantically, and pragmatically correct.Syntactic correctness is easy — does it parse For some fields, there is additional information we can provide beyond what’s available in the schema as well, in particular permissible values that pull from controlled vocabularies.Each field in the index is associated with metadata as seen below, and that metadata is provided as part of the context.Graph Search index representationThe field is derived from the document path as characterized by the GraphQL query.The description is the comment from the GraphQL schema for the field.The type is derived from the GraphQL schema for the field e.g This design strategically balances LLM involvement with more deterministic strategies.End-to-end architectureThe end-to-end process is as follows:A user’s natural language question (with optional `@mentions` statements) are provided as input, along with the Graph Search index contextThe context is scoped by using the RAG pattern on both fields and possible valuesThe pre-processed context and the question are fed into the LLM with an instruction asking for a syntactically and semantically correct filter statementThe generated filer statement DSL is verified and checked for hallucinationsThe final response contains the related AST in order to build “Chips” and “Facets”SummaryBy combining our existing Graph Search infrastructure with the power and flexibility of LLMs, we’ve bridged the gap between complex filter statements and user intent</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:01:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netflixtechblog.com/the-ai-evolution-of-graph-search-at-netflix-d416ec5b1151?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4</guid>
      <source>Netflix TechBlog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metronome + Stripe: Building the future of billing</title>
      <link>https://stripe.com/blog/metronome-stripe-building-the-future-of-billing</link>
      <description>Together, Metronome and Stripe are building the most flexible and complete billing solution on the market—one that works for everyone, from engineers in a garage figuring out their business model to public companies monetizing at global scale.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://stripe.com/blog/metronome-stripe-building-the-future-of-billing</guid>
      <source>Stripe Engineering</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The three biggest agentic commerce trends from NRF 2026</title>
      <link>https://stripe.com/blog/three-agentic-commerce-trends-nrf-2026</link>
      <description>Not only are the majority of retailers actively implementing, or have plans to implement, agentic commerce, but many are also moving to a more tactical phase of optimizing their setup—refining their product catalog strategy to launch faster and investing in their own agentic shopping experiences in addition to integrating with third-party agents.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://stripe.com/blog/three-agentic-commerce-trends-nrf-2026</guid>
      <source>Stripe Engineering</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapting the Facebook Reels RecSys AI Model Based on User Feedback</title>
      <link>https://engineering.fb.com/2026/01/14/ml-applications/adapting-the-facebook-reels-recsys-ai-model-based-on-user-feedback/</link>
      <description>We’ve improved personalized video recommendations on Facebook Reels by moving beyond metrics such as likes and watch time and directly leveraging user feedback We’re doubling down on personalization, tackling challenges like sparse user data [...] Read More The post Adapting the Facebook Reels RecSys AI Model Based on User Feedback appeared first on Engineering at Meta.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:51:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://engineering.fb.com/2026/01/14/ml-applications/adapting-the-facebook-reels-recsys-ai-model-based-on-user-feedback/</guid>
      <source>Meta Engineering</source>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
