<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Engineering Digest</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yourusername/eng-digest</link>
    <description>Daily digest of engineering blog posts from top tech companies</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yourusername/eng-digest/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 09:22:07 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Eng Digest</generator>
    <item>
      <title>Say hello to a new level of interactivity in Gemini CLI</title>
      <link>https://developers.googleblog.com/say-hello-to-a-new-level-of-interactivity-in-gemini-cli/</link>
      <description>We&amp;apos;re excited to announce an enhancement to Gemini CLI that makes your workflow more powerful a...</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 09:22:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://developers.googleblog.com/say-hello-to-a-new-level-of-interactivity-in-gemini-cli/</guid>
      <source>Google Developers</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the Jules extension for Gemini CLI</title>
      <link>https://developers.googleblog.com/introducing-the-jules-extension-for-gemini-cli/</link>
      <description>Introducing the Jules extension for Gemini CLI, an autonomous sidekick for developers It accelerates coding workflows by offloading tasks like asynchronous work, bug fixes, and changes in new branches to Jules, while you stay in flow with Gemini CLI Get started by installing the extension and using the /jules command to initiate and check task statuses.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 09:22:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://developers.googleblog.com/introducing-the-jules-extension-for-gemini-cli/</guid>
      <source>Google Developers</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Request-Response: Architecting Real-time Bidirectional Streaming Multi-agent System</title>
      <link>https://developers.googleblog.com/beyond-request-response-architecting-real-time-bidirectional-streaming-multi-agent-system/</link>
      <description>It advocates for a real-time bidirectional streaming architecture, implemented by the Agent Development Kit (ADK) This streaming model enables true concurrency, natural interruptibility, and unified multimodal processing ADK&amp;apos;s core features are real-time I/O management, stateful sessions for agent handoffs, and streaming-native tools.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 09:22:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://developers.googleblog.com/beyond-request-response-architecting-real-time-bidirectional-streaming-multi-agent-system/</guid>
      <source>Google Developers</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The new identity of a developer: What changes and what doesn’t in the AI era</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/news-insights/octoverse/the-new-identity-of-a-developer-what-changes-and-what-doesnt-in-the-ai-era/</link>
      <description>Discover how advanced AI users are redefining software development—shifting from code producers to strategic orchestrators—through delegation, verification, and a new era of AI-fluent engineering The post The new identity of a developer: What changes and what doesn’t in the AI era appeared first on The GitHub Blog.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 18:15:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.blog/news-insights/octoverse/the-new-identity-of-a-developer-what-changes-and-what-doesnt-in-the-ai-era/</guid>
      <source>GitHub Blog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: AWS re:Invent keynote recap, on-demand videos, and more (December 8, 2025)</title>
      <link>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-aws-reinvent-keynote-recap-on-demand-videos-and-more-december-8-2025/</link>
      <description>The week after AWS re:Invent builds on the excitement and energy of the event and is a good time to learn more and understand how the recent announcements can help you solve your challenges and unlock new opportunities As usual, we have you covered with our top announcements of AWS re:Invent 2025 that you can […]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 17:05:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-aws-reinvent-keynote-recap-on-demand-videos-and-more-december-8-2025/</guid>
      <source>AWS News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to use GitHub Copilot Spaces to debug issues faster</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/ai-and-ml/github-copilot/how-to-use-github-copilot-spaces-to-debug-issues-faster/</link>
      <description>Follow this step-by-step guide to learn how to debug your issues using GitHub Copilot Spaces and Copilot coding agent The post How to use GitHub Copilot Spaces to debug issues faster appeared first on The GitHub Blog.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 20:35:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.blog/ai-and-ml/github-copilot/how-to-use-github-copilot-spaces-to-debug-issues-faster/</guid>
      <source>GitHub Blog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AV1 — Now Powering 30% of Netflix Streaming</title>
      <link>https://netflixtechblog.com/av1-now-powering-30-of-netflix-streaming-02f592242d80?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4</link>
      <description>Today, AV1 powers approximately 30% of all Netflix viewing, marking a major milestone in our efforts to bring more efficient and higher-quality streaming to our members.In this post, we’ll revisit Netflix’s AV1 journey to date, highlight emerging use cases, and share adoption trends across the device ecosystem In March 2025, we launched AV1 HDR streaming We are pleased with the successful progress made, and AV1 with FGS is now supported across a significant and growing number of in-field devices.Looking Ahead: AV1 Today, AV2 TomorrowAs we reflect on our AV1 journey, it’s clear that the codec has already transformed the streaming experience for hundreds of millions of Netflix members worldwide</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 20:09:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netflixtechblog.com/av1-now-powering-30-of-netflix-streaming-02f592242d80?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4</guid>
      <source>Netflix TechBlog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing how SaaS platforms are shipping payments and finance products in days</title>
      <link>https://stripe.com/blog/analyzing-how-saas-platforms-are-shipping-payments-and-finance-products-in-days</link>
      <description>Leading SaaS platforms across industries—from Squarespace to Jobber—are using embedded components to ship payments and finance features with minimal code We analyzed the data to see which types of platforms are getting the most value.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://stripe.com/blog/analyzing-how-saas-platforms-are-shipping-payments-and-finance-products-in-days</guid>
      <source>Stripe Engineering</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your stack, your rules: Introducing custom agents in GitHub Copilot for observability, IaC, and security</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/news-insights/product-news/your-stack-your-rules-introducing-custom-agents-in-github-copilot-for-observability-iac-and-security/</link>
      <description>Use partner-built Copilot agents to debug, secure, and automate engineering workflows across your terminal, editor, and github.com The post Your stack, your rules: Introducing custom agents in GitHub Copilot for observability, IaC, and security appeared first on The GitHub Blog.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:00:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.blog/news-insights/product-news/your-stack-your-rules-introducing-custom-agents-in-github-copilot-for-observability-iac-and-security/</guid>
      <source>GitHub Blog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Bedrock adds reinforcement ﬁne-tuning simplifying how developers build smarter, more accurate AI models</title>
      <link>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/improve-model-accuracy-with-reinforcement-fine-tuning-in-amazon-bedrock/</link>
      <description>Amazon Bedrock now supports reinforcement fine-tuning delivering 66% accuracy gains on average over base models.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:08:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/improve-model-accuracy-with-reinforcement-fine-tuning-in-amazon-bedrock/</guid>
      <source>AWS News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New serverless customization in Amazon SageMaker AI accelerates model fine-tuning</title>
      <link>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-serverless-customization-in-amazon-sagemaker-ai-accelerates-model-fine-tuning/</link>
      <description>Accelerate AI model development with new training features that enable rapid recovery from failures and automatic scaling based on resource availability.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:08:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-serverless-customization-in-amazon-sagemaker-ai-accelerates-model-fine-tuning/</guid>
      <source>AWS News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New features to help SaaS platforms manage risk and stay compliant</title>
      <link>https://stripe.com/blog/new-features-to-help-saas-platforms-manage-risk-and-stay-compliant</link>
      <description>We recently launched three new features that give you more control to fine-tune your risk and compliance strategy, allowing you to use more of Stripe’s data to inform your approach</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://stripe.com/blog/new-features-to-help-saas-platforms-manage-risk-and-stay-compliant</guid>
      <source>Stripe Engineering</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building the future: highlights from Dropbox’s 2025 summer intern class</title>
      <link>https://dropbox.tech/culture/highlights-from-dropbox-2025-summer-intern-class</link>
      <description>The Dropbox Intern Program is thoughtfully designed to cultivate growth, spark innovation, and build lasting connections.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dropbox.tech/culture/highlights-from-dropbox-2025-summer-intern-class</guid>
      <source>Dropbox Engineering</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoomer: Powering AI Performance at Meta’s Scale Through Intelligent Debugging and Optimization</title>
      <link>https://engineering.fb.com/2025/11/21/data-infrastructure/zoomer-powering-ai-performance-meta-intelligent-debugging-optimization/</link>
      <description>We’re introducing Zoomer, Meta’s comprehensive, automated debugging and optimization platform for AI Zoomer works across all of our training and inference workloads at Meta and provides deep performance insights that enable energy savings, workflow acceleration, and efficiency gains in our AI infrastructure The post Zoomer: Powering AI Performance at Meta’s Scale Through Intelligent Debugging and Optimization appeared first on Engineering at Meta.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:00:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://engineering.fb.com/2025/11/21/data-infrastructure/zoomer-powering-ai-performance-meta-intelligent-debugging-optimization/</guid>
      <source>Meta Engineering</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key Transparency Comes to Messenger</title>
      <link>https://engineering.fb.com/2025/11/20/security/key-transparency-comes-to-messenger/</link>
      <description>We’re excited to share another advancement in the security of your conversations on Messenger: the launch of key transparency verification for end-to-end encrypted chats This new feature enables an additional level of assurance that only you — and the people you’re communicating with — can see or listen to what is sent, and that no [...] Read More The post Key Transparency Comes to Messenger appeared first on Engineering at Meta.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 17:00:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://engineering.fb.com/2025/11/20/security/key-transparency-comes-to-messenger/</guid>
      <source>Meta Engineering</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feed blog posts</title>
      <link>https://www.linkedin.com/blog/engineering/feed</link>
      <description>Feed blog postsFeedPutting members first: testing and measuring how content appea...Sakshi JainNov 20, 2025InfrastructureFishDB: a generic retrieval engine for scaling LinkedIn’s feedKenneth LiNov 17, 2025Java heap memory and garbage collection: tuning for high-perfo...Nisheedh RaveendranSep 13, 2024Generative AIHow LinkedIn Built the Engineering Infrastructure to Ignite Pr...Shweta PatiraNov 20, 2023FeedHomepage feed multi-task learning using TensorFlowIan AckermanJun 3, 2021Member/Customer ExperienceHelping members discover communities around interestsChiachi LoSep 17, 2020FeedUnderstanding dwell time to improve LinkedIn feed rankingSiddharth DangiMay 12, 2020FeedRapid experimentation through standardization: Typed AI featur...Ian AckermanApr 15, 2020The Top 2019 LinkedIn Engineering BlogsJaren AndersonDec 9, 2019OptimizationAuditing content features in FollowFeedBanu MuthukumarAug 27, 2019FeedCommunity-focused Feed optimizationJun 25, 2019GroupsCommunities AI: Building communities around interests on LinkedInAbdul Al-QawasmehJun 24, 2019Previous123Next</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.linkedin.com/blog/engineering/feed</guid>
      <source>LinkedIn Engineering</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Optimization With Ax, an Open Platform for Adaptive Experimentation</title>
      <link>https://engineering.fb.com/2025/11/18/open-source/efficient-optimization-ax-open-platform-adaptive-experimentation/</link>
      <description>We’ve released Ax 1.0, an open-source platform that uses machine learning to automatically guide complex, resource-intensive experimentation Our accompanying paper, “Ax: A Platform for Adaptive Experimentation” explains Ax’s architecture, methodology, and how it [...] Read More The post Efficient Optimization With Ax, an Open Platform for Adaptive Experimentation appeared first on Engineering at Meta.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:00:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://engineering.fb.com/2025/11/18/open-source/efficient-optimization-ax-open-platform-adaptive-experimentation/</guid>
      <source>Meta Engineering</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Dash uses context engineering for smarter AI</title>
      <link>https://dropbox.tech/machine-learning/how-dash-uses-context-engineering-for-smarter-ai</link>
      <description>Building effective, agentic AI isn’t just about adding more; it’s about helping the model focus on what matters most.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dropbox.tech/machine-learning/how-dash-uses-context-engineering-for-smarter-ai</guid>
      <source>Dropbox Engineering</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create new monetization opportunities with Stripe Billing’s recent upgrades</title>
      <link>https://stripe.com/blog/create-new-monetization-opportunities-with-recent-stripe-billing-upgrades</link>
      <description>We recently released a series of improvements to expand multiprocessor support, give you more control over your billing and invoicing models, and better tailor your pricing for AI products</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://stripe.com/blog/create-new-monetization-opportunities-with-recent-stripe-billing-upgrades</guid>
      <source>Stripe Engineering</source>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
