<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Engineering Digest</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yourusername/eng-digest</link>
    <description>Daily digest of engineering blog posts from top tech companies</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yourusername/eng-digest/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:40:03 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Eng Digest</generator>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking Peak Performance on Qualcomm NPU with LiteRT</title>
      <link>https://developers.googleblog.com/unlocking-peak-performance-on-qualcomm-npu-with-litert/</link>
      <description>LiteRT&amp;apos;s new Qualcomm AI Engine Direct (QNN) Accelerator unlocks dedicated NPU power for on-device GenAI on Android It offers a unified mobile deployment workflow, SOTA performance (up to 100x speedup over CPU), and full model delegation This enables smooth, real-time AI experiences, with FastVLM-0.5B achieving over 11,000 tokens/sec prefill on Snapdragon 8 Elite Gen 5 NPU.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://developers.googleblog.com/unlocking-peak-performance-on-qualcomm-npu-with-litert/</guid>
      <source>Google Developers</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Gemini API updates for Gemini 3</title>
      <link>https://developers.googleblog.com/new-gemini-api-updates-for-gemini-3/</link>
      <description>Gemini 3 is available via API with updates for developers: new `thinking_level` for depth control, `media_resolution` for multimodal processing, and enforced `Thought Signatures` for agentic workflows, especially with function calling and image generation It also introduces combining Google Search/URL Grounding with Structured Outputs and new usage-based pricing for Grounding Best practices, like using default temperature, are advised for optimal results.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://developers.googleblog.com/new-gemini-api-updates-for-gemini-3/</guid>
      <source>Google Developers</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the Data Commons Gemini CLI extension</title>
      <link>https://developers.googleblog.com/announcing-the-data-commons-gemini-cli-extension/</link>
      <description>The new Data Commons extension for the Gemini CLI makes accessing public data easier It allows users to ask complex, natural-language questions to query Data Commons&amp;apos; public datasets, grounding LLM responses in authoritative sources to reduce AI hallucinations Data Commons is an organized library of public data from sources like the UN and World Bank</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://developers.googleblog.com/announcing-the-data-commons-gemini-cli-extension/</guid>
      <source>Google Developers</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engineering VP Josh Clemm on how we use knowledge graphs, MCP, and DSPy in Dash</title>
      <link>https://dropbox.tech/machine-learning/vp-josh-clemm-knowledge-graphs-mcp-and-dspy-dash</link>
      <description>Engineering VP Josh Clemm deep-dives into how we think about knowledge graphs, indexes, MCP, and prompt optimization using tools like DSPy.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dropbox.tech/machine-learning/vp-josh-clemm-knowledge-graphs-mcp-and-dspy-dash</guid>
      <source>Dropbox Engineering</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From pixels to characters: The engineering behind GitHub Copilot CLI’s animated ASCII banner</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/engineering/from-pixels-to-characters-the-engineering-behind-github-copilot-clis-animated-ascii-banner/</link>
      <description>Learn how GitHub built an accessible, multi-terminal-safe ASCII animation for the Copilot CLI using custom tooling, ANSI color roles, and advanced terminal engineering The post From pixels to characters: The engineering behind GitHub Copilot CLI’s animated ASCII banner appeared first on The GitHub Blog.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.blog/engineering/from-pixels-to-characters-the-engineering-behind-github-copilot-clis-animated-ascii-banner/</guid>
      <source>GitHub Blog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year recap and future goals for the GitHub Innovation Graph</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/news-insights/policy-news-and-insights/year-recap-and-future-goals-for-the-github-innovation-graph/</link>
      <description>Discover the latest trends and insights on public software development activity on GitHub with data from the Innovation Graph through Q3 2025 The post Year recap and future goals for the GitHub Innovation Graph appeared first on The GitHub Blog.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.blog/news-insights/policy-news-and-insights/year-recap-and-future-goals-for-the-github-innovation-graph/</guid>
      <source>GitHub Blog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 learnings from Anders Hejlsberg: The architect behind C# and TypeScript</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/developer-skills/programming-languages-and-frameworks/7-learnings-from-anders-hejlsberg-the-architect-behind-c-and-typescript/</link>
      <description>Anders Hejlsberg shares lessons from C# and TypeScript on fast feedback loops, scaling software, open source visibility, and building tools that last The post 7 learnings from Anders Hejlsberg: The architect behind C# and TypeScript appeared first on The GitHub Blog.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:17:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.blog/developer-skills/programming-languages-and-frameworks/7-learnings-from-anders-hejlsberg-the-architect-behind-c-and-typescript/</guid>
      <source>GitHub Blog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rust at Scale: An Added Layer of Security for WhatsApp</title>
      <link>https://engineering.fb.com/2026/01/27/security/rust-at-scale-security-whatsapp/</link>
      <description>WhatsApp has adopted and rolled out a new layer of security for users – built with Rust – as part of its effort to harden defenses against malware threats WhatsApp’s experience creating and distributing our media consistency library in Rust to billions of devices and browsers proves Rust is production ready at a global scale. [...] Read More The post Rust at Scale: An Added Layer of Security for WhatsApp appeared first on Engineering at Meta.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:00:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://engineering.fb.com/2026/01/27/security/rust-at-scale-security-whatsapp/</guid>
      <source>Meta Engineering</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AI Evolution of Graph Search at Netflix</title>
      <link>https://netflixtechblog.com/the-ai-evolution-of-graph-search-at-netflix-d416ec5b1151?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4</link>
      <description>We need the LLM to generate a Graph Search Filter DSL statement that is syntactically, semantically, and pragmatically correct.Syntactic correctness is easy — does it parse For some fields, there is additional information we can provide beyond what’s available in the schema as well, in particular permissible values that pull from controlled vocabularies.Each field in the index is associated with metadata as seen below, and that metadata is provided as part of the context.Graph Search index representationThe field is derived from the document path as characterized by the GraphQL query.The description is the comment from the GraphQL schema for the field.The type is derived from the GraphQL schema for the field e.g This design strategically balances LLM involvement with more deterministic strategies.End-to-end architectureThe end-to-end process is as follows:A user’s natural language question (with optional `@mentions` statements) are provided as input, along with the Graph Search index contextThe context is scoped by using the RAG pattern on both fields and possible valuesThe pre-processed context and the question are fed into the LLM with an instruction asking for a syntactically and semantically correct filter statementThe generated filer statement DSL is verified and checked for hallucinationsThe final response contains the related AST in order to build “Chips” and “Facets”SummaryBy combining our existing Graph Search infrastructure with the power and flexibility of LLMs, we’ve bridged the gap between complex filter statements and user intent</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:01:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netflixtechblog.com/the-ai-evolution-of-graph-search-at-netflix-d416ec5b1151?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4</guid>
      <source>Netflix TechBlog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon EC2 G7e instances, Amazon Corretto updates, and more (January 26, 2026)</title>
      <link>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-amazon-ec2-g7e-instances-with-nvidia-blackwell-gpus-january-26-2026/</link>
      <description>It’s my first post for 2026, and I’m writing to you while watching our driveway getting dug out I hope wherever you are you are safe and warm and your data is still flowing This week brings exciting news for customers running GPU-intensive workloads, with the launch of our newest graphics and AI inference […]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:25:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-amazon-ec2-g7e-instances-with-nvidia-blackwell-gpus-january-26-2026/</guid>
      <source>AWS News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metronome + Stripe: Building the future of billing</title>
      <link>https://stripe.com/blog/metronome-stripe-building-the-future-of-billing</link>
      <description>Together, Metronome and Stripe are building the most flexible and complete billing solution on the market—one that works for everyone, from engineers in a garage figuring out their business model to public companies monetizing at global scale.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://stripe.com/blog/metronome-stripe-building-the-future-of-billing</guid>
      <source>Stripe Engineering</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Amazon EC2 G7e instances accelerated by NVIDIA RTX PRO 6000 Blackwell Server Edition GPUs</title>
      <link>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-amazon-ec2-g7e-instances-accelerated-by-nvidia-rtx-pro-6000-blackwell-server-edition-gpus/</link>
      <description>AWS introduces Amazon EC2 G7e instances accelerated by the NVIDIA RTX PRO 6000 Blackwell Server Edition GPUs with up to 2.3 times inference performance G7e instances deliver cost-effective performance for generative AI inference workloads and the highest performance for graphics workloads.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:22:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-amazon-ec2-g7e-instances-accelerated-by-nvidia-rtx-pro-6000-blackwell-server-edition-gpus/</guid>
      <source>AWS News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Kiro CLI latest features, AWS European Sovereign Cloud, EC2 X8i instances, and more (January 19, 2026)</title>
      <link>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-kiro-cli-latest-features-aws-european-sovereign-cloud-ec2-x8i-instances-and-more-january-19-2026/</link>
      <description>At the end of 2025 I was happy to take a long break to enjoy the incredible summers that the southern hemisphere provides I’m back and writing my first post in 2026 which also happens to be my last post for the AWS News Blog (more on this later) The AWS community is starting the […]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 00:24:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-kiro-cli-latest-features-aws-european-sovereign-cloud-ec2-x8i-instances-and-more-january-19-2026/</guid>
      <source>AWS News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The three biggest agentic commerce trends from NRF 2026</title>
      <link>https://stripe.com/blog/three-agentic-commerce-trends-nrf-2026</link>
      <description>Not only are the majority of retailers actively implementing, or have plans to implement, agentic commerce, but many are also moving to a more tactical phase of optimizing their setup—refining their product catalog strategy to launch faster and investing in their own agentic shopping experiences in addition to integrating with third-party agents.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://stripe.com/blog/three-agentic-commerce-trends-nrf-2026</guid>
      <source>Stripe Engineering</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapting the Facebook Reels RecSys AI Model Based on User Feedback</title>
      <link>https://engineering.fb.com/2026/01/14/ml-applications/adapting-the-facebook-reels-recsys-ai-model-based-on-user-feedback/</link>
      <description>We’ve improved personalized video recommendations on Facebook Reels by moving beyond metrics such as likes and watch time and directly leveraging user feedback We’re doubling down on personalization, tackling challenges like sparse user data [...] Read More The post Adapting the Facebook Reels RecSys AI Model Based on User Feedback appeared first on Engineering at Meta.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:51:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://engineering.fb.com/2026/01/14/ml-applications/adapting-the-facebook-reels-recsys-ai-model-based-on-user-feedback/</guid>
      <source>Meta Engineering</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSS at Scale With StyleX</title>
      <link>https://engineering.fb.com/2026/01/12/web/css-at-scale-with-stylex/</link>
      <description>It’s no different at Meta, which is why we open-sourced StyleX, a solution for CSS at scale StyleX combines the ergonomics of CSS-in-JS with the performance of static CSS The post CSS at Scale With StyleX appeared first on Engineering at Meta.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:34:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://engineering.fb.com/2026/01/12/web/css-at-scale-with-stylex/</guid>
      <source>Meta Engineering</source>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
